Guide to the School of Fine Arts, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Fine Arts, Yale University, photographs
1880-1950
RU 890
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The rmaterials consist of photographs of class scenes in the Yale School of Fine Arts and sculpture in the Yale Art Gallery.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 18-H (YRG 18-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Art and Architecture and its predecessors.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The rmaterials consist of photographs of class scenes in the Yale School of Fine Arts and sculpture in the Yale Art Gallery.
Art schools; Art students; College art museums; College students; Photographs; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Art Gallery; Yale University. School of Fine Arts
- Photographs documenting the School of Fine Arts
  - Classroom scenes
    - Painting (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sculpting (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gallery (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Art School masque, "Cupid and Psyche,", 1916 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Photograph of Architectural Studios in Yale Art Gallery, circa 1950; Accession 2005-A-031
  - Photograph, circa1950 (Box 1)
- Group photograph of members of the School of Fine Arts, 1929; Accession 2006-A-197
  - Group photograph of members of the School of Fine Arts, 1929 (Box 1)